[Music]
Hello friends.  So friends, in today's
video I will tell you
about ICI Principal Life Insurance.
If you want to get ICI Principal Life Insurance, then do
not do it even by mistake.
You will watch this video completely and I will
tell you how much my minus has been done in this,
which I had deposited only for one year
and I have got a minus of Rs. 10,000 in its retained amount.
Okay
friends?  So you should not get ICI Principal Life
Insurance even by mistake.  So let
me take you first to the fund value.
Ok?  So I'll lower it a little bit.
After this,
I click OK in More Services which is visible here.
After this you have to come down a little further.
After this, if
you want to close this insurance, switch it
, transfer funds,
then this system is also not provided in it.  It will
only be shown here but
you will not be able to transfer funds.  If you
tell the bank to close my
insurance.  He will say that you will have to wait at least 5
years.  So like I had
taken insurance in 2018, the money that we had deposited in it, so
here you
can first see in the fund value,
what is the value of my fund, you
can see that right now my minus is 9000 in it,
it has never increased
friends, only once it was
showing minus 15000, so now it is 2021, it has been
almost 3 years, still there
is minus 9000 in the fund value, so right now
my minus is 9000 in it,
friends.  So you should not take ICI Principal Life Insurance even by mistake.
Insurance means if you do not want to get it done in ICI.
Never have to do it.  If
you want to get insurance, the best option is
SBI Life.  From there you
can get your insurance done in SBI Life.  The returns
are great, friends.  So whenever you
do life insurance, you
must do it with SBI Life.  ICI Prodental
Never Do It In Life.  I am showing you here as
proof.  So I
went to such a bank and we said that we do
not want to follow this policy.  So the bank person flatly refused.
I said, somehow you close it
and transfer the funds to my account.
So he said that nothing is going to happen without 5 years.
So we will have to wait like that for 5 years.
It has been almost 3 years now, I will have to
wait for 5 years.
So friends, if you
want to check your fund value, whether you have done
Prodental Life or have done it by mistake,
then you can check your fund value.  The
bank will tell you many times that
you will get 16, 70, 80% return.  20 can also
mean that you will get 20% return.
But there is nothing like that friends, it only goes into minus.
And during the Corona period,
you do not have to take a policy right now.  Especially
in ICI Bank.  Similarly, I have taken insurance in SBI Life even during the Corona period.
But
still no minus has been seen in that fund
value.  So friends, if you
want to check your fund value, first of all you have to
come to Play Store.
So friends, you have to search ICI Pro LE in Play Store.
Ok?  And after searching,
you can check the fund value, friends.  You will know whether
I am right or wrong.
Okay friends?  If you
liked the video, please like it and if you are
new to the channel, please subscribe.
Thank you.